// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let questions = [  // question for UEFA league 1 to 5
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who has won the Champions League the most?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Barcelona",
      "Manchester City",
      "Liverpool",
      "Real Madrid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who has the most goals in Champions League history?",
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    options: [
      "Lewandowski",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Messi",
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When was the first Champions League?",
    answer: "1955",
    options: [
      "1980",
      "1955",
      "1975",
      "1970"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the only French team to ever win the Champions League?",
    answer: "Olympique Marseille",
    options: [
      "Olympique Marseille",
      "Paris Saint-Germain F.C.",
      "Olympique Lyonnais",
      "AS Monaco"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,  
    question: "Which is the country with the most Champions league titles?",
    answer: "Spain",
    options: [
      "England",
      "Italy",
      "Germany",
      "Spain"
    ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,  // Questions for Premier League Beggining
      question: "Who has won the most Premier League titles?",
      answer: "Manchester United",
      options: [
        "Manchester United",
        "Chelsea",
        "Liverpool",
        "Arsenal"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Who is the top scorer in the premier league of all time",
      answer: "Alan Shearer",
      options: [
        "Wayne Rooney",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Alan Shearer",
        "Sergio Aguero"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which player has provided the most Premier League assists?",
      answer: "Ryan Giggs",
      options: [
        "Frank Lampard",
        "Cesc Fàbregas",
        "David Beckham",
        "Ryan Giggs"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which goalkeeper has the best record in the Premier League?",
      answer: "Petr Čech",
      options: [
        "David James",
        "Petr Čech",
        "Pepe Reina",
        "Edwin Van der Sar"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which team has had the longest unbeaten run at home in the Premier League?",
      answer: "Chelsea - 86 Games",
      options: [
        "Chelsea - 86 Games",
        "Manchester United - 65 Games",
        "Liverpool - 104 Games",
        "West Ham - 62 Games"
      ]
    },

    {
    numb: 11,   // Questions for World Cup Beggining
    question: "Which country have won the most World Cup tournaments trophies?",
    answer: "Brazil",
    options: [
      "Brazil",
      "England",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Who Has scored the most goals in the World Cup?",
    answer: "Miroslav Klose",
    options: [
      "Ronaldo Fenomeno",
      "Maradona",
      "Miroslav Klose",
      "Pele"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is the player that won more World Cups?",
    answer: "Pele",
    options: [
      "Thomas Muller",
      "Miroslav Klose",
      "Ronaldinho Gaucho",
      "Pele"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Who was top scorer at the 2014 FIFA World Cup tournament?",
    answer: "James Rodriguez",
    options: [
      "James Rodriguez",
      "Thomas Müller",
      "Toni Kroos",
      "Messi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which country won the first World Cup?",
    answer: "Uruguay",
    options: [
      "Brazil",
      "Hungary",
      "Uruguay",
      "Italy"
    ]
  },
];